Guide to the Jackie Boschok Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Jackie Boschok papers, 1979-2010; 5688-001; 16.32 cubic feet 22 boxes; 2 oversize folders
  - EDUCATIONAL/TRAINING MATERIALS, SERIES IV
    - Workplace Training Materials, Subseries C
      - Boeing Training Materials: Applied Manufacturing Education Series (AMES) - Master Planning, 2007 (Box-folder 4/20-21)
    - Technology Training Materials, Subseries D
      - Boeing Training Manual: Creating Web Pages with Office 97, 1998 (Box-folder 4/6)
      - New Horizons Training Manual: Microsoft Office Word 2003 - Level 1 (Box-folder 4/13)
      - New Horizons Training Manual: Microsoft Office Outlook 2003 - Level 1 (Box-folder 4/14)
      - IAM Internet Manuals, 2004 (Box-folder 5/11)
    - Sexual Harassment/Domestic Violence/Workplace Violence Resources, Subseries E
      - Guides Re: Sexual Harassment/Domestic Violence/Workplace Violence, circa 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 16/6)
      - Guides Re: Sexual Harassment/Domestic Violence/Workplace Violence, circa 1990s (Box-folder 16/2-5)
      - Sexual Harassment at Work Training Workbook, 1994 (Box-folder 16/1)
      - CLUW Domestic Violence/Sexual Harassment Resources, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 10/10-11)
  - ARTIFACTS, SERIES V
    Series V is divided into nine subseries based on the type of artifact present: Subseries A: Cups and Mugs, Subseries B: Clothing and Hats, Subseries C: Plaques and Trophies, Subseries D: Buttons and Pins, Subseries E: Stickers and Magnets, Subseries F: Tote Bags and Folders, Subseries G: Office/Desk Supplies, Subseries H: Strike Artifacts, Subseries J: Misc. Artifacts. Subseries J is further divided by creating body. Items are arranged chronologically within each subseries, with undated items placed at the end.
    The series includes cups/mugs, clothing, buttons/pins, stickers, office supplies, plaques, trophies and other various items relating to the Jackie Boschok manuscript materials. The bulk of the artifacts are related to the International Association of Machinists (IAM), but the Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW), United Way and Boeing are also represented.
    - Cups and Mugs, Subseries A
      - IAM/Boeing Vocational Solutions glass mug, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 17)
      - IAM/Boeing Quality Through Training Program plastic coffee mug with lid, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 17)
      - Jackie Boschok's mug collection, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 20)
      - Boeing 747-8 reusable cup with lid, circa 2000s (Box 17)
      - IAM Plastic Coffee mug w/ lid, undated (Box 24)
    - Clothing and Hats, Subseries B
      - IAM 751 Making Strides Against Breast Cancer T-shirt & artifacts, 2008 (Box 21)
      - GCIU Union T-shirt, undated (Box 21)
      - IAM T-shirt, undated (Box 21)
      - IAM/Boeing Health and Safety Institute Poncho, undated (Box 17)
      - IAM Hats, undated (Box 24)
    - Plaques and Trophies, Subseries C
      - IAM/MNPL (Machinist's Non-Partisan Political League) Plaque for Jackie' Boschok's completion of Political Training Program, 1994 (Box 17)
      - WSLC Plaque to Jackie Boschok for Outstanding Community Service, 1996 (Box 17)
      - IAM District 751 Guide Dogs of America Golf Tournament Trophy, 2005 (Box 24)
      - United Way Contribution Plaque, undated (Box 17)
    - Buttons and Pins, Subseries D
      - Miscellaneous Coalition of Labor Women's Union (CLUW)/Women's Rights Pins/Buttons, circa 1980s-2000s (Box-folder 19/2)
      - Miscellaneous Union Pins/Buttons, circa 1980s-2000s (Box-folder 19/3)
      - IAM Buttons, undated (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Stickers and Magnets, Subseries E
      - Miscellaneous Union and Women's Stickers, Bumper Stickers and Magnets, circa 1980s-2000s (Box-folder 19/1)
      - Miscellaneous Magnets, undated (Box-folder 24/6)
    - IAM/Miscellaneous Tote Bags and Folders, circa 1996-2011; Subseries F (Box 18)
    - Office/Desk Supplies, Subseries G
      - CLUW 1991 Biennial Convention paperweight (Box 21)
      - IAM Women's Department Planner, 2008 (Box 17)
      - United Way piggy bank, undated (Box 17)
      - United Way calculator, undated (Box 17)
      - United Way mousepad, undated (Box 17)
      - United Way framed calendar, undated (Box 17)
      - Ink pen collection, undated (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Strike Artifacts, Subseries H
      - Strike Scrapbooks, 1989-1995 (Folder:oversize 2)
      - IAM 751 Picket Signs/Posters, 1989-2003 (Folder:oversize 1)
      - IAM 751 Contract/Strike items, undated (Box-folder 22/3)
        Items include: whistles, bank, pin, stickers and a bank.
      - IAM Strike Materials, undated (Box-folder 22)
        Items include: 1 DVD of the 2005 strike, CD-rom of pictures, picket assignments for Jackie & Alex Boschok and a contract sticker board.
    - Miscellaneous Artifacts, Subseries J
      - Part 1: IAM
        - Miscellaneous IAM & IAM 751 items, undated (Box 22)
          Items include: frisbees, stickers, notepads, markers and patches.
        - Miscellaneous IAM Women's Department Artifacts, undated (Box 17)
          Items include: pen necklaces, badge holder and ribbons.
      - Part 2: IAM/Boeing
        - IAM/Boeing Health and Safety Institute Rand Mc Nally Pocket Atlas, 1991-1992 (Box 17)
        - IAM/Boeing Quality Through Training Program pocket dictionary, 1997 (Box 17)
        - Miscellaneous IAM/Boeing and Boeing Company Artifacts, undated (Box 17)
          Items include: ruler, reflectors, calendar, jar grip, paper cutter and magnets.
        - IAM/Boeing Health and Safety Institute "Disaster Pursuits" card deck, undated (Box 17)
        - Miscellaneous IAM/Boeing Artifacts, undated (Box-folder 12/9)
          Items include: monthly dues stamp books, cards/badges and ink stamp.
      - Boeing Employees Community Fund (ECF) glass jar with lid, undated (Box 17)
      - Key chain collection, 1984-2008 (Box-folder 22/5)
      - Seattle Goodwill Games: Soviet Flags, 1990 (Box-folder 17/1)
      - Guide Dogs of America (GDA) Flight For Sight Fun Run Artifacts, circa 2000s (Box-folder 21/1)
        Items include: stickers, towels, ink stamp, runner's bib and lanyard.
      - Miscellaneous United Way Artifacts, undated (Box 17)
        Items include: buttons, letter opener, bookmark and plastic bag.
      - Rosie the Riveter Bobblehead, undated (Box 21)
      - Miscellaneous CLUW Artifacts, undated (Box 21)
        Items include: mugs, water bottle, hat, mouse pad, ruler and flag.
      - Miscellaneous event badges and badge holders, undated (Box-folder 22/1)
- Jackie Boschok papers, 1980-2013; 5688-002; 1.53 cubic feet 5 boxes
  Ephemera, IAM local and district election materials, artifacts relating to Boshock's career at Boeing and as a union officer, including t-shirts from various local and national labor organizations and campaigns. Organizations listed on the t-shirts include the International Association of Machinists, the Coalition of Labor Union Women, and the Washington State Labor Council.
  Donor: Jackie Boschok, August 2013.
  - 1994 IAM District 751 Local Lodge F Officer Election Documents kept by Jackie Boschok, Election Committee Chair; 1995 rerun of IAM 751 Local Lodge F Officer Election by Department of Labor Documents kept by Jackie Boschok, Election Committee Chair (Box-folder 1/1)
  - IAM election materials by candidates for local and District office 1980-2008, Part 1 of 3 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - IAM election materials by candidates for local and District office 1980-2008, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - IAM election materials by candidates for local and District office 1980-2008, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Misc items that belong with materials previoulsy donated. Contact me if more info is necessary (Box-folder 1/5)
  - 2 Boeing 'Vendor' badges for full-time IAM officials and an annual Boeing parking pass issued to Jackie Boschok (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Note: Items listed below are in one of the four boxes. (Box-folder BOXES 2-5)
  - 1987 TESC First Annual Summer School for Trade Union Women t-shirt
  - 1988 CLUW American Family Celebration t-shirt
  - 1988 TESC Second Annual Summer School for Trade Union Women t-shirt
  - 1989 UMWA Camp Solidarity t-shirt
  - 1990 Rotary Goodwill Games jacket, 1989
  - 1991 CLUW Seattle Convention t-shirt
  - 1991 TESC Olympia, WA Summer Institute for Union Women t-shirt
  - 1992 Vancouver, BC Summer Institute for Union Women t-shirt
  - 1993 CLUW Las Vegas Convention t-shirt
  - 1993 UPIU Lockout t-shirt
  - 1994 Puget Sound chapter CLUW 20th Anniversary Celebration t-shirt
  - 2003 CLUW Seattle Convention t-shirt: Vision,Voices, Votes
  - 2007 CLUW Las Vegas Convention t-shirt
  - 2009 CLUW Los Angelas Convention t-shirt
  - 2010 United Way of Snohomish County Day of Caring t-shirt
  - Boeing Everett AOG (Aircraft on the Ground)/SPARES organization t-shirt circa 1990's
  - CLUW Voting Women t-shirt
  - CLUW with logo t-shirt
  - CLUW Women's Place t-shirt
  - MUSA Puerto Rico t-shirt from CLUW NEB held there
  - SCLC Operation Shortfall t-shirt
  - UFW Boycott Chateau St. Michelle t-shirt
  - WSLC Women's Committee 'A Woman's Future in in Her Union' t-shirt
  - WSLC Women's Committee personalized shirt
  - WSLC Women's Committee 'Women in Unions' t-shirt